loadtop.com 2011-12-19

# Loadtop.com - Free Games, Themes, Ringtones and Applications for mobile phones

**Privacy Policy**

We do not sell, trade, rent or make available, your personal information to others.

This Privacy Policy outlines how your personal information is treated and forms part of our Terms & Conditions Of Use. We may occasionally modify our Privacy Policy; when this happens we will notify you via our Terms of Use page. 

What information do we collect? 

When you complete a form on our website, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, postal address and your telephone number(s). This is so we can contact you easily if required. 

How do we use your information? 

We use the information collected from you to help in any issues you may have relating to this website. We may use your personal information to communicate with you, for record keeping purposes, and in aggregate (and therefore anonymously) for market research purposes, to track activity on our site, to publish trends and/or to improve usefulness and content. 

Advertisers:

  * We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. Google and other ad companies, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to www.loadtop.com.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to the website users based on their visit to www.loadtop.com and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 
  * Third-party vendors and ad networks are also serving ads on this website. So cookies of other [third-party vendors or ad networks](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) may also be used to serve ads on this site.
  * You may visit[ those websites](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) to opt out of cookies (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). You can opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website at [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

Cookies 

Cookies are small text files that a web site transfers to a site visitor's hard disk or browser for added functionality, or for tracking web site usage. We do not use cookies to gather personal information such as a person's name or e-mail address. In order to measure the effectiveness of our on-line presence, Mobile Heart may use cookies to identify repeat visitors to our site and to determine the path visitors take on our site. 

Use of cookies is an industry standard and many web sites use them. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you can set your web browser to do so, if your browser so permits.

Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We use state of the technology to track intruders and maintain our site active and protected. 

Children's Privacy

Some Portions of the Web site may be used by children under the age of 13. We are strongly committed to protecting the safety and privacy of children who visit our web site. 

## » Popular Android Games

Sort by name | rating | date

  Contract Killer (3,06M)

  Gold racing (1,8M)

  Racing Live (1016,1K)

  Drag Racing (6,55M)

  Raging Thunder (2,44M)

  Raging Thunder 2 (2,13M)

  iCommando (14,56M)

  Epic Truck 3D (11,72M)

  Deer Hunter African Safari (2,82M)

  Deadly Chambers (10,91M)

  Sniper Vs Sniper (12,4M)

  BitBlocks (44,1K)

  Bug Village (2,21M)

  The Sims 3 (2,17M)

  Virtual Horse Racing (12,71M)

1 | [2](http://loadtop.com/android_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/rating/860/?pg=1) | [3](http://loadtop.com/android_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/rating/860/?pg=2) | .. | [8](http://loadtop.com/android_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/rating/860/?pg=7) (1-15 from 112) 

## » Popular iPhone Games

Sort by name | rating | date

[ ](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179057/) [Trial Xtreme](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179057/) (13,14M)

[ ](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179052/) [MicroPool](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179052/) (1,16M)

[ ](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179058/) [iBoat Racer](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179058/) (31,82M)

[ ](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179055/) [Hard Racing](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179055/) (27,02M)

[ ](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179029/) [Angry Birds](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179029/) (14,5M)

[ ](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179056/) [Bike Baron](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179056/) (36,29M)

[ ](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179046/) [Durak](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179046/) (28,22M)

[ ](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179053/) [Mad Skills Motocross](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179053/) (17,27M)

[ ](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179054/) [Hockey Fight Pro](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179054/) (83,68M)

[ ](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179042/) [Cubes](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179042/) (4,34M)

[ ](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179031/) [Doodle Jump](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179031/) (18,96M)

[ ](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179059/) [Virtual Villagers 4 The Tree of Life](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179059/) (34,73M)

[ ](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179051/) [Action Bowling](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179051/) (13,29M)

[ ](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179030/) [Castle Clout](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179030/) (18,43M)

[ ](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179083/) [Enemy Alert!](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/get/5179083/) (5,97M)

1 | [2](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/rating/870/?pg=1) | [3](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/rating/870/?pg=2) | [4](http://loadtop.com/iphone_games/index.php?z=downloads/ngame/rating/870/?pg=3) (1-15 from 48)
